Anh Tien Nguyen

CONTACT Information Homepage: anhtienng.github.io Email: ngtienanh@korea.ac.kr

RESEARCH INTERESTS My research interest is **deep learning in medical image analysis**, especially **computational histopathology**. My current research focuses on whole slide image analysis, such as cancer sub-typing, metastasis detection, and survival prediction.

EDUCATION

Korea University, South Korea

03/2023 - present

M.Sc., Computer Engineering

- GPA: 4.38/4.5
- Supervised by Prof. Jin Tae Kwak
- Research area: computational pathology

Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology, Vietnam

08/2017 - 08/2021

B.E., Computer Engineering

- GPA: 9.26/10 Rank 2
- Graduation classification: Excellent

PUBLICATIONS

- Anh Tien Nguyen, Trinh Thi Le Vuong, and Jin Tae Kwak Towards a text-based quantitative and explainable histopathology image analysis In *Medical Image Computing and Computer-Assisted Intervention* (MICCAI), 2024 Early accept, top 11%
- Anh Tien Nguyen, Keunho Byeon, Kyungeun Kim, Boram Song, Seoung Wan Chae, and Jin Tae Kwak

CAMP: Continuous and Adaptive Learning Model in Pathology Journal - Under review, 2024

• Anh Tien Nguyen and Jin Tae Kwak

GPC: Generative and General Pathology Image Classifier

In Medical Image Computing and Computer-Assisted Intervention (MICCAI) Workshop, 2023

Best Paper Honorable Mention Award

RESEARCH EXPERIENCES

Korea University, South Korea

03/2023 - present

Research assistant

- Main research topics: computational pathology.
- Projects:
 - An unified framework for pathology image classification
 - Text-based embeddings for pathology images

Olli Technology, Vietnam

06/2020 - 09/2020

Research intern

• Researched and built a Text-to-Speech model to generate Vietnamese natural voice with fast inference speed.

TEACHING EXPERIENCE

Korea University, Korea

Teaching assistant - C programming language

Industry experiences Cloud Ace, Vietnam

10/2021 - 02/2023

Machine learning engineer

• Designed and deployed machine learning solutions on Google Cloud Platform.

• Taught machine learning courses on Google Cloud Platform.

SKILLS

Programming: Python, PyTorch, OpenSlide

Tool: QuPath

English: IELTS 7.5

Awards

KU Foreign Global Leader Scholarship

08/2024

Achieved a for excellent GPA, research projects, and publications.

BK21 Scholarship

03/2024

Achieved a scholarship for excellent research projects and publications.

KU Natural Science and Engineering scholarship

03/2023 - 06/2024

Achieved a scholarship for excellent research projects and publications.

Honda Award

03/2021

Achieved top 100 nationwide scholarship for Science and Technology students based on merit and research.

HCMC University of Technology scholarship

08/2017 - 08/2021

Achieved scholarships for outstanding students who ranked 5% in a class.

FPT Digital Race

10/2020

Ranked 3^{rd} by designing and deploying an autonomous vehicle control system.

CERTIFICATIONS

Google Cloud Authorized Trainer

03/2022

Authorized to teach the track of data and machine learning.

Coursera Deep Learning Specialization

03/2020

Finished a foundation course on deep learning.

REFERENCES

• Assoc Prof. Jin Tae Kwak

School of Electrical Engineering, Korea University

Email: jkwak@korea.ac.kr

• Assoc Prof. Tho Thanh Quan

Acting Dean, Faculty of Computer Science and Engineering, HCMC University of

Technology

Email: qttho@hcmut.edu.vn